iberiabank.com 2008-12-16

# IBERIABANK

Tuesday, December 16, 2008

##  New Deposit Insurance Limits 

On October 3, 2008, FDIC deposit insurance temporarily increased from $100,000 to $250,000 per depositor through December 31, 2009.

##  Easy Switch Kit 

Click for our [Easy Switch Kit](http://www.iberiabank.com/pdfs/pdfLibrary/Switchkitonline.pdf).

##   e-Statements 

Go Paperless... what a great way to view your statements anytime. Learn More!

  * Reorder Checks Online
  * Learn More About Online Banking
  * Deluxe Gift Card

This is IBERIABANK’s Privacy Notice for our consumer customers also referred to in this Notice as our client or clients. IBERIABANK is committed to providing quality products and services in an environment that protects consumer privacy rights. We respect the right to privacy of our clients, applicants for our products and services and individuals visiting us on-line. We are committed to protecting confidentiality of the information furnished to us by our clients and our former clients. 

This Notice describes the types of information we collect, how we use the information, and how we protect your confidential information. This Notice is subject to change. You can always review our current Privacy Notice on our web site at www.iberiabank.com, or visit any of our offices to obtain a copy. 

Facts | 

### **WHAT DOES IBERIABANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
---|---  
What? | 

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us, including information shown on consumer credit reports and from your application. This information can include: 

  * social security number and income 
  * account balances and payment history 
  * credit history and credit scores 

---|---  
How? | All financial companies need to share clients’ personal information to run their everyday business - to process transactions, maintain client accounts, and report to credit bureaus. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their clients’ personal information; the reasons IBERIABANK chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.   
---|---  
**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does IBERIABANK share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes –** to process your transactions, maintain your account, and report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes** – to offer our products and services to you  | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** – information about your transactions and experiences  | Yes | No  
**For affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes _(Complete opt out form)_  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –** information about your creditworthiness or from your applications with us | Yes | Yes _(Complete opt out form)_  
**For non-affiliates to market to you** | Yes | Yes _(Complete opt out form)_  
**Sharing practices**  
---  
**How often does IBERIABANK notify me about their practices?** | We must notify you about our sharing practices when you open an account and each year while you are a client.   
**How does IBERIABANK protect my personal information?** | We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need access in the course of doing business and/or to provide you with the products or services you need. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.   
**How does IBERIABANK collect my personal information?** | 

We collect your nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:

  * information we receive from you on forms when you request a product or service;
  * information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others;
  * information we receive from consumer reporting agencies; and,
  * information collected by the use of “cookies” on some of our web pages. We use cookies to determine how many people visit our site which enables us to improve the design and content. Information that we collect through the use of cookies is subject to this Notice.

**Why can’t I limit all sharing?** | 

Federal law gives you the right to limit sharing only for: 

  * affiliates’ everyday business purposes-information about your creditworthiness 
  * affiliates to market to you based on your personal information that we collect
  * non-affiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.   
**Definitions**  
**Everyday business purposes** | 

The actions necessary by financial companies to run their business and manage client accounts, such as

  * processing transactions, mailing, and auditing services
  * providing information to credit bureaus 
  * responding to court orders and legal investigations 

**Affiliates** | 

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Our affiliates include banks, mortgage compaines, insurance companies, and securities brokerages._

**Non-affiliates** | 

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Non-affiliates we share with can include mortgage companies, insurance companies, direct marketing companies, and nonprofit organizations._

**Joint marketing** | 

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * _Our joint marketing partners include reputable companies for the purposes of informing you about products and/or services they offer. Our partners may be financial service providers, direct marketing firms or other companies such as non-profit organizations._

**Sharing practices**  
**Contact us** | 

**By mail:**Print this mail-in form (PDF), mark your choices, fill in and send form to: 

Customer Privacy Control Desk  
IBERIABANK  
P.O. Box 12440  
New Iberia, LA 70562-2440  
  
Member **FDIC** | Equal Housing Lender
